Betty Wilke Cox papers, Inclusive: 1896-2007, undated, Bulk: 1970-2006, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
Betty Wilke Cox papers
Inclusive: 1896-2007, undated, Bulk: 1970-2006, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
3860
Cox, Betty Wilke, 1928 - 2006
29 document boxes
Betty Wilke Cox was a writer, editor, and publisher based out of Austin, Texas. Her collection includes manuscripts, correspondence, personal journals, research material, photographs, and biographical information.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Betty Jean Wilke Cox was born on 1928 September 25 in Fort Worth, Texas to L.A. Wilke and Viola Helen Anderson Wilke. L.A. Wilke was a respected journalist and Texas newspaper editor who deeply influenced his daughter's future career choices. In 1944, Betty Cox graduated from Gainesville High School in Gainesville, Texas. She then attended Texas Woman's University in Denton, Texas, from which she received her bachelor's and master's degrees. After graduating, she initiated her writing career as a newspaper reporter for the Nolan County News and the Sweetwater Reporter in the late 1940's. Later, she taught briefly in Dallas and Del Valle, Texas, before pursuing the library science field. Cox worked as a librarian at the Austin Public Library, the Texas State Library, the Texas A&M University Special Collections Library, and the Ocotillo Branch Library in Phoenix, Arizona.
Following her retirement, Cox founded Woodburner Press, which she ran in conjunction with her editing business, Hudman Editing Service in Austin, Texas. Through Woodburner Press, she published fourteen of her client's books, several of which are housed in The Texas Collection. Her own book, Liz Carpenter: Girl from Salado, was published in 1994 by Eakin Press.
Betty passed away on 2006 August 28 in Austin, Texas.
Scope and Content
This collection is divided into five series. The largest is the Hudman Editing Service/Woodburner Press series, which includes documents and correspondence Cox collected from the editing and/or publishing services she provided for various clients. Literary Productions, the second largest series, consists primarily of Cox's personal written work, with some pieces coming from other authors or unknown authors. The next series, Personal Materials, includes a variety of materials pertaining to Betty's life such as personal records, employment history, correspondence, photographs, and journals. The bulk of the fourth series, Family Documents, is comprised of correspondence between Betty Cox and her son Mike Cox, as well as some of his creative works and personal materials. This series also holds cards, photographs, and correspondence from other family members. General Research is the final series and it includes Cox's collected research materials that she gathered possibly for her own work or her clients, though none of the original folder titles specified which.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, there was neither a chronological order or topical order to the folders and documents in this collection, although some related content was grouped together. Several documents were loose and unlabeled. Some rearrangement was necessary. Original folder contents were maintained if all of the content was related. Many of the folders in this collection retained their original title. A title was created only if the original title did not accurately describe the folder's content or if an original title was not present.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 3860. Acquired 2013-08-09
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Mike Cox collection, Inclusive: 1913-2014, Bulk: 1985-2005
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Cox, Betty Wilke -- Archives.; Cox, Betty Wilke. Assembly of suspects.; Cox, Betty Wilke. Liz Carpenter.
Subjects (Organizations)
Hudman Editing Service (Austin, Tex.) -- Records and correspondence.; Woodburner Press (Austin, Tex.) -- Records and correspondence.
Subjects
Women authors -- Archives.; Women editors -- Texas -- Archives.; Women printers -- Texas -- Archives.
Genres
Photographs.
- Hudman Editing Service/Woodburner Press, 1985-2006; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The bulk of this series contains correspondence, manuscripts, and research materials for several of Cox's clients. These items are in the first subseries, "Clients." The second and final subseries, "Other," houses papers pertaining to the daily operations of Hudman Editing Service and Woodburner Press such as invoices, newsletters, service descriptions, and sales tax permits. This series is in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Cassette tape; Floppy disk (3.5"); Photographic print
  - Clients, 1988-2006; 1
    - Barlow, Stacey, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (1 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (2 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (3 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (4 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (5 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (6 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (7 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bludworth, Rosa: Love Came Tricklin' Down (8 of 8), 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Boatman, Clyde and Joseph Lay (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Boatman, Clyde and Joseph Lay (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Canales, Rudy, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Cox, Bruce and Dennis (1 of 5), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cox, Bruce and Dennis (2 of 5), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cox, Bruce and Dennis (3 of 5), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Cox, Bruce and Dennis (4 of 5), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cox, Bruce and Dennis (5 of 5), 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Curtis, Terry, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dysart, Norman: Like Whispers in the Wind, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Eccles, Rita, 2003 March 28 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Engel, Paul: The Black Queen, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Fox, James Donald: The Aviator (1 of 3), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Fox, James Donald: The Aviator (2 of 3), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Fox, James Donald: The Aviator (3 of 3), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Fox, James Donald: A Summer to Remember, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Gann, Harvey E.: Escape I Must! (1 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Gann, Harvey E.: Escape I Must! (2 of 2), 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Jamison, Bob: Airplanes, Alligators, and Hi-Fin Blues, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (1 of 12), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (2 of 12), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (3 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (4 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (5 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (6 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (7 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (8 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (9 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (10 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (11 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Jamison, Bob: Law West of the Trinity (12 of 12), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Miller, Violet: The Carterstown Ghosts: Chapter 5, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Correspondence (1 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Correspondence (2 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Correspondence (3 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Correspondence (4 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Correspondence (5 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Research (1 of 2), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Research (2 of 2), 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Miller Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Revisions (1 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Revisions (2 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Revisions (3 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Revisions (4 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Miller, Violet and Aliya Ma Lynn: Kuli's Iron Trail: Revisions (5 of 5), 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Modisett, Bill: J. Evetts Haley: A True Texas Legend, 1995 October 12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Musson, Lamar: Slavery in Corporate America, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Northcutt, Jimmy, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Looking Back: Invoices, 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Running High, Looking Good: Invoices (1 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Running High, Looking Good: Invoices (2 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Running High, Looking Good: Invoices (3 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Osborne, W.C.: Running High, Looking Good: Promotional Material, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Peacock, Darnell: Oil Field Trash (1 of 3), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Peacock, Darnell: Oil Field Trash (2 of 3), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Peacock, Darnell: Oil Field Trash (3 of 3), 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Rothman, Carolyn: There's Always Hope (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Rothman, Carolyn: There's Always Hope (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Correspondence (1 of 4), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Correspondence (2 of 4), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Correspondence (3 of 4), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Correspondence (4 of 4), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Invoices, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Partial Manuscript (1 of 5), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Partial Manuscript (2 of 5), 1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Partial Manuscript (3 of 5), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Partial Manuscript (4 of 5), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Partial Manuscript (5 of 5), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Promotional Material (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Rothman, Carolyn and Michael: Your Journey's Destiny: Promotional Material (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Sherrill, Diane: Second Voice: Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sherrill, Diane: Second Voice: Invoices (1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Sherrill, Diane: Second Voice: Invoices (2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Sherrill, Diane: Second Voice: Promotional Material, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Ruby: Sam Willard: Manuscript (1 of 5), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Ruby: Sam Willard: Manuscript (2 of 5), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ruby: Sam Willard: Manuscript (3 of 5), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Ruby: Sam Willard: Manuscript (4 of 5), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Ruby: Sam Willard: Manuscript (5 of 5), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Complete Book (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Complete Book (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Correspondence (1 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Correspondence (2 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Correspondence (3 of 3), 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Notes, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Preparatory Work (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Preparatory Work (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Research (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Smith, Ruby: Wine, Cheese, and Bread: Research (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Correspondence (1 of 3), 1995-2002 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Correspondence (2 of 3), 1995-2002 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Correspondence (3 of 3), 1995-2002 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Family Records, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Illustrations, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (1 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (2 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (3 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (4 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (5 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (6 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (7 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (8 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (9 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (10 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (11 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (12 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Partial Manuscript (13 of 13), undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Promotional Material, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Recipes, undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Research (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Stewart, Ozella: Just Me: Research (2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Texas Press Messenger Project, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Correspondence (1 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Correspondence (2 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Correspondence (3 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Correspondence (4 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Correspondence (5 of 5), 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Illustrations (1 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Illustrations (2 of 4), undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Illustrations (3 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Illustrations (4 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Invoice, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (1 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (2 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (3 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (4 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (5 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Partial Manuscript (6 of 6), 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Promotional Material, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Research (1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Waldon, Lewis: A Dog Called Friday: Research (2 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Articles (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Just Plain Red: Manuscript (1 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Just Plain Red: Manuscript (2 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Just Plain Red: Manuscript (3 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Just Plain Red: Manuscript (4 of 4), undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Personal Photographs (1 of 2), 1934-1993 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Personal Photographs (2 of 2), 1934-1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Waldon, Lewis: Short Stories, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Waldon, Lewis: The War Party, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Illustration, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (1 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (2 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (3 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (4 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (5 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (6 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (7 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (8 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (9 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (10 of 11), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Wallace, Ruth: The Snowbird: Manuscript (11 of 11), 1999-2006 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Wallace, Ruth: A Study in Courage, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Complete Book, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Correspondence (1 of 3), 1984-2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Correspondence (2 of 3), 1984-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Correspondence (3 of 3), 1984-2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Illustrations (1 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Illustrations (2 of 2), undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (1 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (2 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (3 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (4 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (5 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (6 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (7 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Manuscript (8 of 8), 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Wallace, Ruth: Wings 'n Things: Photographs, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Williams, Mildred Fleischer: Gus: Manuscript (1 of 4), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Williams, Mildred Fleischer: Gus: Manuscript (2 of 4), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Williams, Mildred Fleischer: Gus: Manuscript (3 of 4), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Williams, Mildred Fleischer: Gus: Manuscript (4 of 4), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Will: 3D Objects, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (1 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (2 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (3 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (4 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (5 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (6 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (7 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (8 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (9 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (10 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (11 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (12 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (13 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (14 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (15 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (16 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (17 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Wilson, Will: Devil Take the Hindmost: Manuscript (18 of 18), 1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (1 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (2 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (3 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (4 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (5 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (6 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (7 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (8 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (9 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (10 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (11 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Will: A Fool for a Client: Manuscript (12 of 33), 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)